Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- A cardinal, school staff and teachers during school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref960)
  Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Advertisements; Schools/Education; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Religious Crosses; Audiences/Spectators; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A teacher giving a speech. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref961)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Color Photography; Microphones; Speeches; Schools/Education; Awards; Ceremonies; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
- Award ceremony. 10.1 x 14.9 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref962)
  Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Cameras; Women; Ceremonies; Awards; Flags; Color Photography; Crowds; Teachers; Medals/Insignia; Schools/Education; Group Portraits
- Man presenting award. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref963)
  Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Awards; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Women; Men; Group Portraits
- Group portrait. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref964)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Color Photography; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Award ceremony. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref965)
  Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Medals/Insignia; Awards; Ceremonies; Teachers; Students; Boys; Scouts; Children; Men; Group Portraits
- Two men in the audience at a school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref966)
  Teachers; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Crowds; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Men; Audiences/Spectators; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Carpets/Rugs; Facial Hair
- Nun/teacher receiving an award in a school event. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref967)
  Women; Men; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Nuns; Helwan, Egypt; Awards; Boys; Color Photography; Teachers; Girls; Children; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits
- Students playing football in the school playground. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref968)
  Sports; Football; Outdoors; Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Audiences/Spectators; Color Photography; Children; Group Portraits
- Students playing football in the school playground. 14.8 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref969)
  Football; Boys; Sports; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Boys behind a fence. 14.8 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref970)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Boys; Children; Uniforms; Group Portraits
- A group photo of nuns and clergymen/school staff in a Collège de la Sainte Famille event. 14.8 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref971)
  Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Men; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Priests/Clergymen; Nuns; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Three men holding awards, posing alongside school staff. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref972)
  Men; Awards; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Police; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- A Cardinal giving a speech. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref974)
  Religious Crosses; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Speeches; Schools/Education; Men; Microphones; Group Portraits
- Student giving a speech in an honoring ceremony. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref975)
  Schools/Education; Teachers; Awards; Men; Microphones; Students; Speeches; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Children
- A large group of students. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref976)
  Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Children
- Two men sitting at a desk. 14.8 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref977)
  Offices; Telephones; Men; Color Photography; Drinks/Beverages; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings
- A man and woman sitting at a desk. 15 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref978)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Offices; Color Photography; Drinks/Beverages; Men; Women; Group Portraits
- Three men sitting in a room. 15 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref979)
  Drinks/Beverages; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Men; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Group photo of school staff. 14.9 x 10.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref980)
  Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Drinks/Beverages; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Food; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Children; Facial Hair
- A hand-colored postcard of Al-Tewfiqi Mosque. 15 x 10.1 cm, 1884 (Object AD_MC_028_ref981)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Color Photography; Mosques; Religious Sites; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
- Staff in an office at the school. 13.5 x 18.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref982)
  Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Offices; Awards; Photographic Prints; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Staff in an office at the school. 18 x 11.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref983)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Offices; Men; Awards; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- School building. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref984)
  Buildings; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Outdoors; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Class photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref985)
  Group Portraits; Teachers; Students; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Children; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in the school playground. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref986)
  Children; Boys; Outdoors; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students playing football in a field. 4.1 x 6.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref987)
  Landscapes; Sports; Football; Photographic Prints; Students; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Children; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Human pyramid in school grounds. 9.7 x 14.2 cm, 1946 (Object AD_MC_028_ref988)
  Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Children; Boys; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
- A man with two clergymen. 5.5 x 5.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref989)
  Gardens; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
- Student group photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref990)
  Uniforms; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A group of students posing on the steps of a building. 6.2 x 9.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref991)
  Boys; Children; Buildings; Group Portraits; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Three members of school staff. 7.4 x 10.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref992)
  Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students posing in theatrical costumes on 'Theatre day'. 6.2 x 9 cm, 20 November 1948 (Object AD_MC_028_ref993)
  French Writing; Theater; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Telescope; Children; Schools/Education; Boys; Hats; Costumes; Men; Group Portraits
- School event with Egyptian and British flags flying. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref994)
  Schools/Education; Fez/Tarboush; Students; Hats; Audiences/Spectators; Women; Flags; Nuns; Men; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Boys and men in the desert. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref995)
  Boys; Animals; Donkeys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Men; Deserts; Students; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits
- Students and teachers on field trip. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref996)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Outdoors; Students; Boys; Italian Writing; Men; Group Portraits
- Woman sitting on bench during school trip. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref997)
  Outdoors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Teachers; Schools/Education; Boys; Water; Photographic Prints; Students; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Individual Portraits; Group Portraits
- A portrait of high school student. 8.7 x 6 cm, 5 February 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref998)
  Schools/Education; Boys; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait at a school field trip. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref999)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Rivers; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Water; Boats/Ships; Uniforms; Students; Teachers; Boys; Coast; Schools/Education
- Group portrait during a school trip. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1000)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Palm Trees; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Teachers; Boys; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Schools/Education
- Group portrait during a field trip. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1001)
  Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Donkeys; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Boys; Men; Students; Teachers; Hats; Animals; Children; Rivers; Nile River; Boats/Ships; Uniforms
- Two men posing in front of a boabab (tabaldi) tree. 6 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1002)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Buildings; Men; Sudan; Italian Writing; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Houses
- The interior of a church. 8.8 x 6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1003)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Paintings; Religious Crosses; Architecture; Churches; Boys; Children
- Boys stand next to a tent in the desert. 6 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1004)
  Deserts; Landscapes; Boys; Tents; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Children; Group Portraits; Outdoors
- Group portrait of a family. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1005)
  Photographic Prints; Girls; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Palm Trees; Outdoors; Parks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Italian Writing; Children
- A mixed group sit on blankets on the ground. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1006)
  Men; Girls; Group Portraits; Women; Palm Trees; Parks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Picnic; Boys; Outdoors; Children
- Boys on a paddle boat. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1007)
  Lakes; Children; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Parks; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Outdoors; Boys; Students; Boats/Ships; Water; Teachers; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait during field trip. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1008)
  Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Students; Teachers; Boys; Men; Italian Writing; Children; Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Group portrait during school trip. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1009)
  Men; Students; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Children; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Teachers; Schools/Education
- Boys on a paddle boat. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1010)
  Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Lakes; Helwan, Egypt; Parks; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Men; Water; Students; Boys; Boats/Ships; Schools/Education; Children
- Group portrait during field trip. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1011)
  Schools/Education; Italian Writing; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Men; Teachers; Boys; Students; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
- Hieroglyphic inscriptions on Edfu temple. 10.2 x 14.9 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1012)
  Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Edfu, Egypt; Italian Writing; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
- A portrait. 4.7 x 3.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1013)
  Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men
- A portrait. 5 x 4.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1014)
  Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Italian Writing; Facial Hair
- A portrait. 6.4 x 4.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1015)
  Uniforms; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints
- A portrait. 6.3 x 4.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1016)
  Facial Hair; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Studio Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A portrait. 6 x 3.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1017)
  Men; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
- Postcard of the George Nuncovich hotels. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1890 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1018)
  English Writing; Italian Writing; Donkeys; Camels; Hotels; Postcards; Buildings; Animals; Springs; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Men; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits
- A car accident. 9 x 14 cm, 13 October 1979 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1019)
  Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Nuns; Transportation; Women; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits
- Car accident. 9 x 14 cm, 13 October 1979 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1020)
  Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Cars/Trucks; Helwan, Egypt; Transportation; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing
- Car accident. 9 x 14 cm, 13 October 1979 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1021)
  Helwan, Egypt; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Women; Streets/Roads; Outdoors; Transportation; Cars/Trucks; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Car accident. 9 x 14 cm, 13 October 1979 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1022)
  Streets/Roads; Outdoors; Cars/Trucks; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Transportation
- Inside the school's theatre. 8.8 x 12.9 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1023)
  Theater; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Paintings; Furnishings; Schools/Education
- Map explaining the pharaonic typography of Helwan and neighboring regions. 10.6 x 8.8 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1025)
  Maps; Paintings; Italian Writing; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Egypt; English Writing; Arabic Writing; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Printed Materials
- Painting depicting ancient Egyptian deities Horus and Seth. 9.4 x 8.9 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1026)
  Arabic Writing; English Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Paintings; Italian Writing
- Painting of Pharaoh Narmer's (or Menes) Palette in a classroom. 10.4 x 8.8 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1027)
  Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Paintings
- Painting illustrating an ancient Egyptian story (?). 9.9 x 8.8 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1028)
  Photographic Prints; Paintings; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
- Painting of a map showing the location of Helwan, Per Hapi and Memphis. 10 x 8.8 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1029)
  Helwan, Egypt; Maps; Paintings; Schools/Education; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Photographic Prints; Color Photography
- Church in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1890 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1030)
  Italian Writing; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Churches; Architecture
- Building in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1031)
  Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Streets/Roads; Men; Women; Buildings
- Group portrait of nuns. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1931 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1032)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Women; Schools/Education; Nuns; Religious Crosses; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Nubar Street in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1033)
  Streets/Roads; Outdoors; Religious Sites; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Mosques; Buildings
- Class photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1970 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1034)
  Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Schools/Education; Religious Crosses; Students; Teachers; Nuns; Group Portraits; Women; Italian Writing; Girls; Photographic Prints
- Girls dressed in Japanese kimono costumes. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1947 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1035)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Girls; Costumes; Italian Writing; Students; Group Portraits; Hand Fans; Umbrellas/Parasols; Children; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Girls in school dormitory. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1036)
  French Writing; Children; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Nuns; Students; Schools/Education; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Chidren wearing Bavarian/Austrian style costumes. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1037)
  Photographic Prints; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Costumes; Children; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Students; Germany; Boys; Girls; French Writing; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- Students on a bridge in the Japanese garden. 9 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1917-1920 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1038)
  Outdoors; Boys; Students; Gardens; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Water; Bridges; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Parks; Photographic Prints; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Group Portraits
- Group portrait of students on school trip to Japanese garden. 13.9 x 9 cm, Circa 1917-1920 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1039)
  French Writing; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Parks; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Students
- Group portrait on a beach. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1948 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1040)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Umbrellas/Parasols; Schools/Education; Boys; Men; Water; Students; Beaches; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Children; Seas
- Students on a rock posing. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1041)
  Men; Outdoors; Boys; Teachers; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Deserts; Children; Schools/Education
- Landscape of the Japanese garden in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1917-1920 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1042)
  Parks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Gardens; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors; Statues/Sculptures; French Writing
- Students in the Japanese garden. 9 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1917-1920 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1043)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Parks; Palm Trees; Boys; Outdoors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Students; Gardens; French Writing; Children; Group Portraits; Schools/Education
- Statues in the Japanese garden in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1917-1920 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1044)
  Statues/Sculptures; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ponds; Parks; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Outdoors; Water; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Ponds; Bridges; Palm Trees; Landscapes
- The school's church. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1045)
  Buildings; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Streets/Roads; Outdoors; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Churches
- Students and teachers in front of a bus. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1046)
  Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Men; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Outdoors; Students; Teachers; Italian Writing; Buses; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Transportation; Facial Hair
- Students in a pyramid formation. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1946 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1047)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Students; Flags; Schools/Education; Boys; Sports; Architecture; Teachers; Children; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Carpets/Rugs; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair
- School football team. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1951 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1048)
  Football; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Students; Outdoors; Boys; Sports; Children
- Students exercising. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1049)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Schools/Education; Sports; Outdoors; Italian Writing; Students; Group Portraits; Students
- Boys posing on the sphix of Saqqara. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1951 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1050)
  Helwan, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Students; Children; Boys; Group Portraits; Saqqara, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Uniforms; Palm Trees; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints
- Field trip to Ain Helwan. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1051)
  Helwan, Egypt; Springs; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Outdoors; Water; Uniforms; Students; Teachers; Italian Writing; Boys; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Children; Hats; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Helwan observatory. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1903 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1052)
  Buildings; Uniforms; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Observatories; Italian Writing; Schools/Education; Students; Group Portraits
- Students in theatrical costumes. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1053)
  Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Swords/Knives; Hats; Facial Hair; Costumes; Students; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Children; Performance Plays; Weapons; Theater; Helwan, Egypt
- Priests posing in front of cars in the desert. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1932 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1054)
  Hats; Cars/Trucks; Priests/Clergymen; Italian Writing; Deserts; Photographic Prints; Transportation; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair
- Group photo of students and teachers. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1935 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1055)
  Italian Writing; Girls; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Students; Gelatin Silver Prints; Teachers; Boys; Men; Children
- Class portrait. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1951 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1056)